{
    "questions":[
        {
            "question": "Which event occurs when the user clicks on an HTML element?",
            "options": ["onchange", "onmouseclick", "onclick", "onmouseover"],
            "answer": "onclick",
            "id": "0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which event occurs when the user moves the mouse over an HTML element?",
          "options": ["onmouseover", "onchange", "onclick", "onmousemove"],
          "answer": "onmouseover",
            "id": "1"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which event occurs when an input field is changed?",
            "options": ["oninput", "onchange", "onfocus", "onblur"],
            "answer": "onchange",
            "id": "2"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which event occurs when an HTML form is submitted?",
            "options": ["onchange", "onsubmit", "onload", "oninput"],
            "answer": "onsubmit",
            "id": "3"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which event occurs when an HTML element loses focus?",
            "options": ["onblur", "onfocus", "onchange", "oninput"],
            "answer": "onblur",
            "id": "4"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which event occurs when the user scrolls an HTML element?",
            "options": ["onscroll", "onmove", "onwheel", "onresize"],
            "answer": "onscroll",
            "id": "5"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which event occurs when the user double-clicks on an HTML element?",
            "options": ["onmouseover", "ondblclick", "onclick", "onmouseout"],
            "answer": "ondblclick",
            "id": "6"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which event occurs when the browser has finished loading the page?",
            "options": ["onload", "onunload", "onready", "onstart"],
            "answer": "onload",
            "id": "7"
          },
          {
            "question": "Which event occurs when the user presses a key on the keyboard?",
            "options": ["onkeydown", "onkeypress", "onkeyup", "oninput"],
            "answer": "onkeypress",
            "id": "8"
          },
          {    
            "question": "Which event occurs when an HTML form is submitted?",
            "options": ["onchange", "onsubmit", "onload", "oninput"],
            "answer": "onsubmit",
            "id": "9"
          }
    ]
}